- Are you done?
- No.
(Sheldon:)Despite what the name suggests...
(Sheldon:)...the civet cat is not a true cat.
(Sheldon:)Now I'm done.
You know what? I'm thinking Howard
wasn't making a back-scratching metaphor.
(Raj:)I'm thinking there was some
actual scratching involved.
(Leonard:)What about it, Howard?
Okay, I didn't wanna say anything...
...because I know you and Leslie
have a little history.
- I don't care about that.
- Great, I'm dying to say something.
(Leonard:)You and Leslie?
In the paintball shed. Twice.
(Sheldon:)Is that why you didn't cover our escape
and let us get cut down like animals?
(Howard:)Oh, yeah. Sorry about that.
(Sheldon:)My good man.
(Sheldon:)Dereliction of duty in the face of
the enemy is a court-martial offense.
Court martial, schmort martial.
(Howard:)Leslie Winkle is the fifth girl
I've ever had sex with.